MSTS New Roads Route Builders Kit, Version 3.2 (UK)
by Bruce Bridges, Martyn T. Griffin, Steven Masters, Jeff Rice

WHAT'S NEW
Not much, assembled textures into one zip file.

CREDITS
Bruce Bridges - Custom Roads (Conrail Indy)
Martyn T. Griffin - Gravel Roads, Residential City Roads
David Kuntz - Yellow Stripe
Dickey Tarkington - Cracked Pavement Texture
Jason Webb - Brick Road Texture

DESCRIPTION
A small set of shapes is included with this route builders kit to cover any small gaps that appear between road sections.

Gravel Roads (included with permission)
   These road section objects are in essence clones from the standard MSTS road shapes and Dirt road shapes. Other than to rename the shape and image references to isolate them and adjusting sizes for the single lane sections, all that is really different is the ACE images used.
   They make use of already existing section indexes 0 thru 3 and 207 thru 224 as needed.
   The intent is to portray country roads and driveways that have been routinely covered with 1/4" to 1/2" gravel.

Residential City Roads (included with permission)
   These road sections are to be used for creating city housing 'suburbs', schools, parks and the occasional corner 7/11 store.
   They consist of an Asphalt road 6 meters wide (2 lanes) with cement curbs along the sides. They also contain sidewalks that are just over 1 meter wide, and a 2 1/2 meter wide outlawn (boulevard) between the sidewalk and curbs. The outlawn area is transparent, resulting in the terrain texture being used for the lawn.
   Manhole covers are to be found at each major intersection and at each dead end court.

In addition, the following static objects are included:
- rd2ldrventcty.s
	- a driveway entrance (from road to sidewalk) that is 3.8 meters 
	  wide tapering to about 2.9 meters wide. It must be placed 
	  manually (ie: via F3) over top of the outlawn transparency 
	  area. It is placed initially at about .05 meters higher than 
	  the road section. Adjust as needed after placing.
- rd2ldrvwaycty.s
	- a driveway section (beyond sidewalk) that is 2.9 meters 
	  wide and 5.8 meters long. Several may be needed for a 
	  full driveway. It must be placed manually (ie: via F3) 
	  over top of the lawn area beyond the sideway. It is 
	  placed initially at about .05 meters higher than 
	  the road section. Adjust as needed after placing.
- crosswalk.s
	- a 6 meter long double white stripe to be places at 
	  intersections or anywhere two opposing sidewalks approach 
	  the road.
- hydrant01.s
	- a short fire hydrant typically found along residential 
	  outlawn areas. This one has the caps painted yellow and 
	  is about 26 inches high.
- hydrant02.s
	- a tall fire hydrant typically found in older residential 
	  areas and in commercial areas. This one has the caps 
	  painted white and stands up to 44 inches high.
- mailbox.s
	- This is a USPS curbside style mailbox designed for drive 
	  up mailing of letters and small packages. It is typically 
	  placed along an outlawn where it can be reached through a 
	  car window.

INSTALLATION
1) Unzip the file.
2) Copy '*.ace' files to your route's appropriate 'texture' folders.
3) Optional - Copy '*.s' and '*.sd' to your route's 'shapes' folder. Add the "add-to.ref" to the route's 'ref' file.

LEGAL/QUESTIONS/COMMENTS
You are allowed to use these sections in routes of your own design if you so choose, provided that any distribution is free of charge and proper credit is given where it is due.

For all other questions, requests, and/or comments, contact me at:
s_masters@shaw.ca

Thank you for downloading!
